At ICIC [music] Lombard, we ensure a
seamless property claims process.
Once [music] you report a loss, our
experts assist the damage, finalize the
report, [music] and handle all
documentation.
Initiatives to digitize [music] the
journey for a seamless process.
One, digital claim [music] information
via multiple channels.
Two, virtual surveys.
Three, minimal digital [music]
documentation.
Four, OTP based check assessment
approval.
[music] and five penny drop technology
for account verification.
[music] At ICICI Lombard, we simplify
property claims with smart technology,
ensuring [music] a quick, transparent,
and hassle-free claim settlement
process. [music]
>> [music]